UTU New York State Legislative Director Files 5711
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UTU New York State Legislative Director Files
1955-1977
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Transportation Union (UTU)
5711
20 cubic feet
20 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3122968
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 07, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5141: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Records 5622: UTU New York State Legislative Board Selected Files 5623: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Legislative Board of New York Files
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.; United Transportation Union.
3122968
- Legislative Files. 1955-1966. (Box 1)
  - Senate Int. 2055, Assembly Int. 2727: Amendment to Labor Law, in relation to rules of Board of Standards and Appeals affecting railroad, Pullman and Express employees, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: Maintenance and Equipment of a Caboose and/or Rider Car (electric lighting facilities), 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: General, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: Close Clearance, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Senate Int. 1390, Assembly Int. 3154: Print 1446 to Amend the Tax Law, Print 3301 in relation to the optional 10 percent deduction, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: Weekly Pay Bill, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Senate Int. 2665, Print 2894; Assembly Int. 3861, Print 4319: Legislation to amend Section 49 of the Public Service Law to determine method of rate fixing for Railroad Companies, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Weight-Distance Law, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Senate Int. 2250, Print 2448; Assembly Int. 2620, Print 2775: Amends Section 54 Railroad Law Maintenance and Equipment of Passenger Cars, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Legislation regarding Section 28, Sanitary Law and Section 196, Weekly Pay Law. Definition of word "employee", 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: To amend tax law, relation to allowance of a credit to a resident for taxes paid other states for the taxes upon and with respect to personal incomes., 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: To amend Public Service Law, in relation to power of Public Service Commission to order continuance or restoration of train services where direct operating costs of train can be shown to exceed aggregate gross revenues to be derived therefrom, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Senate Int. 911, Print 940: Amending Public Authorities law of New York City Transit Authority regarding status of employees covered by labor agreement., 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Scope and Contents
    Also Senate Int. 2422, Print 2511: regarding fees for medical examination as condition of employment. Assembly Int. 1642, Print 1681: Amend Labor Law regarding cashing of checks
  - Int. 2876, Print 2988 (Drumm Bill): To amend existing labor law to prohibit use of economic pressure or organizational picketing to coerce any person or employee to join a particular labor organization, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Assembly Int. 3653m Print 3795: Amend Labor Law relation to power of Board of Standards and Appeals to make variations from rules, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Introduced by Mr. Podell
  - Legislation: Hughes-Ashbery Unemployment Insurance Bill, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: Amends 54-b, Railroad Law, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Amends 54-b, Railroad Law, to include passenger train with fuel-electric engines in provision that it shall be manned with not less than one engineer, one fireman or helper, and to provide that there shall be an assistant or co-engineer.
  - Assembly Int. 863, Print 872; Senate Int. 583, Print 599 (Bauer-Ostrander Bill): Equipment of track motor cars used by railroads for transporting employees, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Legislation: (Grade Crossing) To amend Railroad Law, in relation to the performance of work; division of expense; accounting; claims for damage; valuation, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Legislation: An act to amend the public service law, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    An act to amend the public service law, in relation to the duty of the commission to provide protective measures for employees of railroad and railway express operations in cases of abandonments, mergers, and consolidations.
  - Legislation: Close Clearance Legislation, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Senate Bill introduced by Mr. Milmoe, Assembly Bill introduced by Mr. McMullen.
  - Legislation: Insurance, 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Legislation: Amend Railroad Law, relation of clearance distances between adjacent tracks and between tracks and adjacent overhead structures, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Senate 267, Print 267 (Long Island Railroad): Regarding proposed fare increase in passenger rates; amendment requires prior PSC approval., 1958 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Introduced by Senator Duffy
  - Governor's Committee on Improper Labor and Management Practices: Questions for Discussion at Public Hearing, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    December 16, 1957
  - Legislation: To amend tax law, in relation to allowance of credit to resident for taxes paid to other states for taxes with respect to incomes, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Legislation (General): To provide more adequate assistance to the blind - certain labor bills and other legislative bills, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Assembly Int. 1869, Print 1890; Senate Int. 1891, Print 1987 (Track Motor Car), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Assembly bill introduced by Ostrander; Senate bill introduced by Bauer
  - Legislation: New York State Income Tax Law, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Legislation: Convalescent Care Policies. Senate Int. 1438 to amend Section 250; Assembly Int. 1881 regarding insurance laws., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Senate Bill introduced by Brydges, Assembly Bill introduced by Brook
  - Legislation: General, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Labor Racketeering Bill: Senate Int. 3687 Prints 4258 and 4267; Assembly Int. 4330, Print 4907, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Legislation: Miscellaneous Bills, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Int. 1234 Print 1235: To amend Executive Law in regards to the creation of an office of transportation within the executive department, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Legislation: Railroad Tax Bills, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Budget Bill Assembly 2818, Print 2874 (Same as Drumm Bill Assembly 2945, Print 3001), 1960 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    To amend the tax law in relation to the allowance of a credit to a resident for taxes paid to other states for taxes upon and with respect to personal income. Also includes other bills.
  - Election Law: Application of law relative permitting railroad employees two hours off from actual service in order to vote in public elections, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Legislation: Repeal of Section 1986 of Penal Law, relating to placing passenger cars in front of other railroad cars, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Legislation: Labor Bills, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Legislation: Insurance, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Legislation: Time off for voting, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Senate Introduced 513, Print 513: Concurrent resolution in Senate and Assembly regarding the purchase and rental commuter railroad cars by Port Authority New York, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Assembly Int. 3054 Print 3129: Amendment to Caboose Law, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Senate Resolution 24; Assembly Resolution 64: Investigate Railroad freight-passenger service, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Introduced by Harold A. Jerry, Junior and Edwyn E. Mason, respectively.
  - Senate Print 3320 Int. 3090; Assembly Print 4662 Int. 4415: World Trade Center, Hudson and Manhattan Tubes, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Questionnaire: Resolution Senate 24, Assembly 64, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Senate Int. 2724 Print 2894; Assembly Int. 3384 Print 3481: "Hoffa" Bill, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    Senate Bill introduced by Cooke, Assembly Bill by Manley
  - Legislation: Miscellaneous Bills, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Insurance Bills, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Assembly Int. 2330 Print 2339: Motor Car Bill, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Introduced by Assemblyman Curto
  - Miscellaneous Bills, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Senate Int. 1426 Print 1446; Assembly Int. 2411 Print 2432: Caboose Law Amendment, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Senate Resolution 82 (Laverne), Assembly Resolution 102 (Goddard): Investigate Finances and Services: New York State Railroads, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Senate Int. 2413 Print 2507 (McEwen); Assembly Int. 3482 Print 3552 (Curto): Job Protection Bill, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Senate Int. 3296 Print 3524 (Thaler); Assembly Int. 2996 Print 3041 (Chananau): "Safety" Bill, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Senate Int. 1278 Print 1281 (Laverne); Assembly Int. 1664 Print 1667 (Goddard): Pennsylvania Railroad-New York Central Merger, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Senate Int. 3296 Print 3524 (Thaler); Assembly Int. 2996 Print 3041 (Chananau): Amend labor law to include "safety" in scope of code 42, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Senate Int. 3379 Print 3642 (R. Cooke); Assembly Int. 4307 Print 4483 (Waters): Motor Vehicles, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Miscellaneous Bills, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Bills regarding the repeal of Railroad Tax Relief, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Senate Int. 4518 Print 5457 and Assembly Int. 5997 Print 6943 (Rules Committee): Metropolitan Commuter Transit Authority, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Mass Transportation: Commuter Bills, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Senate Int. 4301 Print 4809 and Assembly Int. 5780 Print 6342: An act to amend law in relation to franchise on employee welfare plans, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Senate Int. 2501 Print 2609 (Hoak); Assembly Int. 2070 Print 2070, 3823 (Waters): Safety code - transportation to and from places of employment, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Senate Int. 3894 Print 4286: Diesel exhaust fumes covered terminals, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Anti-air pollution bills, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Senate Int. 2879 Print 3035 and Assembly Int. 3346 Print 3384: Inspection and calibration of tachographs, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Senate Int. 2878 Print 3034 and Assembly Int. 3442 Print 3480: Standees on certain omnibuses, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Bills Affecting Bus Lodges, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Bills to amend Election Laws, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Senate Int. 2457 Print 2561 (Glinski); Assembly Int. 4030 Print 4121 (Lis): Retention of rights for employees after acquisition of railroads, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Assembly Int. 1715 Print 1715 (Chananau): "Safety" within Code 42 Labor Law, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Assembly Int. 3547 Print 3585 (Griffin): Amend railroad law to require a flagman, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Senate Int. 1864 Print 1913 (Laverne) and Assembly Int. 3440 Print 3515 (Stockmeister): hearing required on train discontinuances, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Senate Int. 1934 Print 1989 (Glinski) and Assembly Int. 2561 Print 2618 (Lis): Track inspection bill, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Assembly Int. 3546 Print 3584 (Griffin): Amend Labor Law - weeds, debris, etcetera, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Assembly Int. 4348 Print 4502 (Griffin): Flag Protection Bill, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Weeds, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Amendment to 51-b Public Service Law to require hearings, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Assembly Int. 2355 Print 2405 (Lis): Obstruction of Crossings, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Air pollution, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Senate 1153 (Bernstein), Assembly 3271 (Chananau): Standees on Busses, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Repeal Railroad Law 54-b, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Senate 3335A (Gordon Bill), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Assembly Int. 2010 Print 2050 (Chananau): Safety Code Rule 42, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Track Inspection and Maintenance, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Assembly Int. 3505 Print 3580 (Corbett): Caboose Law Amendments, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Senate Int. 1640 Print 1685 (Bernstein) and Assembly Int. 2009 Print 2049 (Chananau): Standees on certain motor buses, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Senate Int. 2457 Print 2561 (Glinski): Retention of rights after acquisition of railroads, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Senate Int. 1640 Print 1685 (Bernstein) and Assembly Int. 2008 Print 2048 (Chananau): Tachographs, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Senate Int. 419 Print 419 (Mackell) and Assembly Int. 1358 Print 1358 (Mardesca): New York City Transportation Authority, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Senate Int. 1933 Print 1988 (Glinski) and Assembly Int. 2560 Print 2617 (Lis): Motor Vehicle Transportation Railroad Workers, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Protection Measures Public Service Committee, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    No date - 1966?
  - Senate Int. 2786 Print 2879 (Speno) and Assembly Int. 4335 Print 4489 (Emery): 10 dollar registration fee for school buses, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Retention of Rights Omnibus, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Senate 2025 (Gordon) and Assembly Int. 4681 Print 4889 (Waryas): Flag Bill, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Rochester Port Authority Development and Improvement, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Spark Arresters: Locomotives, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Senate 1288 (Bernstein) and Assembly Int. 2327 Print 2343 (Altman): Speed recorders - buses, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Senate 2485 (Griffin) and Assembly 2429 Print 2445 (Lis): Motor Vehicles used to transport railroad workers, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Senate Int. 1827 Print 1855 (Glinski) and Assembly Int. 3266 Print 3291 (Lis): Amend penal law - obstructing crossings, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Senate 2326 (Glinski) and Assembly Int. 3086 Print 3151 (Lis): Lights on Switches, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Senate 2178 (Hughes) and Assembly Int. 3002 Print 3067 (Greco): Markers on last car of train, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Senate 1320 (Glinski); Assembly 1310 Print 1310 (Lis); Assembly 2339 Print 2355 (Lis): Retention Rights of Railroad Employees, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Transportation Act Bond Issue, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 106)
- Legislative Files. 1967-1970. (Box 2)
  - Bills: 1961 Session of the Legislature (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Senate 5300 (Griffin): Close Clearance Law Amendment, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Senate 2940 (Griffin) and Assembly 4873 (Griffin): Lights on Switches, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Local Lodge Correspondence to Assemblymen and Senators, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Senate 387 (Adams), Assembly 555 (Long): Repeal Tax Relief, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Senate 2201 (McGowan, Griffin), Assembly 2389 (Lis): Transportation of railroad employees via motor vehicles and inspection thereof, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Senate 2444 (Powers), Assembly 3464 (Stockmeister): Investigation of railroad accidents, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    January 30, 1968
  - Unibill Senate 391 (Bloom), Assembly 529 (Lama): "Garnishee" law, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    January 3, 1968
  - Senate Int. 1952 Print 2001 (Hoak); Assembly Int. 3175 Print 3250 (Hogg): Retention of rights for bus employees, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    1966?
  - Senate 1157 (Flynn), Assembly 1157 (Walsh): Propulsion of Missiles, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    February 18, 1969
  - School Bus Bills, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    January-March 1968
  - Senate 737 (McGowan), Assembly 1351 (Chananau): Dangerous Acts, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    January 8, 1969; February 17, 1970
  - Senate 2202 (McGowan, Griffin); Assembly 2390 (Lis, Stockmeister): Track Inspection Bill, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    January 1968
  - Senate 1910 (Bernstein), Assembly 4550 (Chananau): Standees on Buses, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    January-February 1968
  - Assembly 4223 (Greco): Markers on last car of trains, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    February 1968
  - Assembly 3353 (Blumenthal): Diesel Fumes, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Proposed Caboose Law Amendment, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: Miscellaneous, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - ICC (Illinois Commerce Commission) Docket 50586: Inadequate Flagging Hearing, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Senate 63 (Griffin), Assembly 1927 (Lis): Close Clearances, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Senate 3510 (Glinski), Assembly 1928 (Lis): Retention of Rights, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    February 1969
  - Vetoed Bills, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Long Island Railroad Crash, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    November 22, 1950
  - Railroad Association-Railroad Brotherhood Bills: Highway Crossing, etcetera, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Senate 2451 (Thaler), Assembly 2787 (Chananau): Safety in Code 42, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Senate 2184 (Bernstein), Assembly 4551 (Chananau): Tachographs, Buses, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    January 1969
  - Assembly 4821 (Chananau): Protection on Trains, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Senate 707 (Powers), Assembly 3465 (Stockmeister): Proposed Section 51b discontinuance of trains, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Senate 2570 (Glinski), Assembly 3026 (Lis): Retention of rights for railroad employees, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    January 24 1968
  - Senate 2174 (Gordon), Assembly 2831 (Lis): Flag Bill, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    January 23, 1968
  - Senate 2093 (Thaler), Assembly 2959 Print 3024 (Chananau): Code 42, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    January 1967
  - Senate 233 (Garcia), Assembly 473 (Mondello): Vegetation Bill, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Proposed Legislation, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Assembly 5223 (Gilman, D.W. Cook): Missile Bill, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    February 17, 1970
  - Senate 667 (Powers), Assembly 1790 (Corbett): Electric Markers, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Also Assembly 5421
  - Legislative Affair, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    February 10, 1970. Includes route map.
  - Legislative Affair: Mario's Theatre-Restaurant, Troy, New York, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    March 18th, 1969.
  - Senate 1513 (Bernstein), Assembly 2432 (Lis): Bus Standees, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    Also Assembly 2751 (Chananau)
  - Senate 3096 (Galiber), Assembly 804 (Mercorella): Jury Duty Payments, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Consolidated Rail Corporation, Northeast Region: General Order 720, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    Bound. Published April 14, 1976. Effective 2:00AM Sunday April 25, 1976.
  - Senate 2488 (Griffin and Powers), Assembly 1549 (Lis): Train Line Length, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Legislative Files. 1969-1970. (Box 3)
  - Rules Board of Standards and Appeals 1969-70 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bus Tacit graphs 1969-70 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Control of Exchange Fumes (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Light Switches 1969-70 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Public Service Commission - Discontinuance of Trains 1969 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Railroad Police Weapons 1970 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Long Island Power 1969-70 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Standards: Public Service Commission 1970 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Vegetation and Debris 1969-70 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Flagging 1968-70 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Electric Worker Bill 1969-70 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - First Aid Kit Bill 1969-70 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Meal Period Legislation 1967-70 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Railway Safety Bill 1969-70 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Proposed Legislation 1969 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Proposed Legislation 1969 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Memos in Opposition 1970 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Transportation Committee Meeting - March 2, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Bills Discussed by Jerry Rogers and Steven H. Rice (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Misc. Bills 1968-69 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Legislative Files. 1970-1973. (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - An Act to Create the New York State Intercity Railroad Corporation, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Radio and Television Coverage, Notes, etcetera, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report of the Chairman of the Legislative Board, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Bound
  - Honorable Don W. Cook, Chairman Assembly Sub-Committee on Railroads, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Joint Legislative Committees, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Memorandums (Used) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Releases, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Memorandums, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Proposed Legislation, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Senate 6563, Assembly 115-A: Repeal Section 54b, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Session Correspondence, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Mary Roberts versus G.W. Rogers, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Code 42: Safety, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Includes photographs
  - Diesel Fumes Grand Central Terminal, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Senate 7981 A (McGowan): Railroad Crossing Legislation, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Assembly 186 (Chananau), Senate 2044 (Bernstein): Bus Speed Recorder Bill, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Assembly 403 (Ginsberg), Senate 537 (Giuffreda): Motor Vehicle Sand, Stone Cover Bill, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Assembly 1425 (Carroll), Senate 1734 (Laverne): Meal Period Bill, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Assembly 2440 (Tills and Mondello): Vegetation and Debris Bill, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Assembly 6900 (Cook): Proposed State Takeover of Passenger Service, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    March 10, 1971
  - Assembly 1813 (Lis) and Senate 1589 (Giffin): Train Line Length Bill, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Flagging, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Includes Photograph
  - Light Switches, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    September 27, 1970
  - Obstruction of Crossings, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Jury Duty, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Meal Periods, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Railroad Safety, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Train Line Length, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Includes Newspaper Clippings and Photographs
  - Memorandums to be cut and run (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Assembly 1812 (Lis) and Senate 1895 (Bernstein): Bus Standee Bill, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Assembly 1588; Assembly 1589; Assembly 1916 and Senate 1385: Air Pollution and Exhaust Fumes Bill, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Assembly 1588; Assembly 1589; Assembly 1916 and Senate 1385: Air Pollution and Exhaust Fumes Bill, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Vegetation and Debris, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Senate 8296 (Barclay) and Assembly 9479 (Taylor): Reflectorized Markers, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    February 28, 1972
  - Assembly 2369 (Lis): Obstruction of Railroad Crossing Bill, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Insurance Bills: Senate 7195, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    January 5, 1972
  - Assembly 1436 (Corbett) and Senate 484 (Gordon): Flagging Bill, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Assembly 1699 (Mercorella) and Senate 363 (Dunne): Jury Duty Bill, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Assembly 691 (Kelleher) and Senate 709 (Hudson): Lights on Main Track Switches, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Assembly 1811 (Lis) and Senate 1557 (Griffin): Railroad Safety Bill, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Assembly 171 (Cook), 185 (Chananau); Senate 1303 (Thaler): Standards and Appeals Bill, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - A Statement Relative to the Full Crew Law of New York State (Box 4, Folder 43)
    Bound Pamphlet. No date.
  - The Coal Facts of Life (Box 4, Folder 44)
    Bound Pamphlet. 2 copies. No date.
  - Assembly 6499: To amend the transportation law, etcetera, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    March 26, 1970. Bound.
  - Locomotive Inspection, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Assembly 558 (Cook), Senate 248 (Gordon): Flagging Bill, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Jury Duty Bill, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 48)